Graves, Rhoda Fox; Papers apap364
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Rhoda Fox Graves Papers
1906-1948
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap364
14.03 cubic ft.
This collection documents Rhoda Fox Graves' service in the New York State Assembly and Senate. It also contains some personal materials from her life.
Collection X
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives from the Gouverneur Museum, 2016 June 30.
Historical Note
Rhoda Fox Graves (1877-1950) was prominent in public affairs in the North Country of New York and the first woman elected to New York State Senate. Graves was first elected to the New York State Assembly from St. Lawrence County in 1924 and served from January 1, 1925 until December 31, 1932. She held that positon longer than any woman of her time. Two years later, she was elected to the New York State Senate where she served continuously until she resigned in ill health December 31, 1948.
Rhoda Fox married Perle A. Graves in 1905 and had two sons, Paul and Marcus. All three survived her. When she resigned from her State Senate seat, Paul was elected to succeed her.
Graves achieved a number of firsts in her career. She was the first woman to become vice president of the St. Lawrence County Republican Committee. She was the first woman to be elected from a northern county to the New York State legislature. She was the first woman to serve in the New York Sate Senate, the first woman to preside over that legislative body, and to head a Senate Standing Committee (Agriculture).
Scope and Contents
The Rhoda Fox Graves Papers contain records that were generated during her time as a representative of Northern New York in the State Assembly and State Senate. The collection is heavy in correspondence, both professional and personal, mostly regarding matters of importance to her constituents such as agriculture. Included are legislation, campaign materials, and committee records. The collection also contains scrapbooks, subject files, and artifacts.
Arrangement of the Collection
Original order was maintained or reclaimed when possible, but a majority of the collection was disorganized so an order was imposed.
The Assembly Files are in their original alphabetical order. The Senate Files are arranged chronologically and the Subject Files are arranged alphabetically.
Rhoda Fox Graves; Politicians--New York (State); Correspondence; Bills (legislative records); Files by subject; New York (State). Legislature. Senate. Standing Committee on Agriculture; New York (State). Temporary Economy Commission; The State of New York Joint Committee on Farm-to-Market Roads; New York (State). Legislature. Assembly; New York (State). Legislature. Senate; Joint Legislative Committee to Investigate Mineral Waters of the State; Daughters of the American Revolution. New York Organization; Women's National Republican Club (U.S.)
- Assembly Files, 1906-1932; 1; 3.4 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  Rhoda Fox Graves' personal and political papers are interfiled. Much of what is contained in these records are correspondence between her constituents and fellow legislators, legislative bills, and pamphlets distributed by various Republican organizations. Personal letters and records reflecting daily activities are included as well as files dating before her election into the Assembly.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically. There are two files for each letter, each with different dates. This reflects Rhoda Fox Graves' original filing system while integrating the two distinct groupings.
  - 200th Anniversary of the Birth of George Washington - Pamphlet and Article, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - A, 1922-1923; 1925-1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A, 1926-1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Acts to Amend Legislation, 1931-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Bulletin, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The American Foundation Pamphlets, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Democratic Nursery Rhymes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Are You Voting Communist or American?" Pamphlet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Articles About Cavemen by Harold Whitnall, 1923; 1926 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Assembly Bills, 1926-1932 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - B, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - B, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bills and Constituent Letters, 1925-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bills and Correspondence: Labor, 1929-1930; 1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - C, 1920; 1924-1924; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Canada: Debates of the Senate, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Chapters of New York State Law, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Civic, State and Community Advertising, 1927-1929; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Militarism in Education: "So This is War" Pamphlet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Dairy, 1927; 1931-1933; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Creation of New Park Region and Commission, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - D, 1923-1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - D, 1928-1931; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - E, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - F, 1925-1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Farm-To-Market Roads (1 of 2), 1906; 1927; 1929-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Farm-To-Market Roads (2 of 2), 1906; 1927; 1929-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Farm-To-Market Roads, 1906; 1927; 1929-1932; Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - The Foreign Policy Association Speakers Bureau Pamphlet, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Fraternal Order of Eagles Old Age Pensions Pamphlet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - G, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - G, 1928-1931; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Great Lakes--St. Lawrence Tidewater Association Pamphlet, 1926-1927; 1929-1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - H, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - H, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Highway Lighting, 1929; 1931-1932; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - I, 1926-1927; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - J, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - J, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - K, 1924-1927 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - K, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Killed Senate Bills, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Knight & Bostwick, 1930-1931 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - L, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - L, 1929-1930; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Legislation, 1926; 1928-1929; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence (1 of 2), 1924; 1931; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence (2 of 2), 1924; 1931; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence (1 of 2), 1931-1932; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence (2 of 2), 1931-1932; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: St. Lawrence County, 1927-1932 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - List of Assembly Members, 1925-1926; 1928-1929 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - List of Assembly Members, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Litigation to Apply the Merit System"-- Good Government Pamphlet, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - M, 1922; 1924-1927; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - M, 1927-1930; Undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Marcus Graves, 1926-1931; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Members and Officers of the New York State Legislature, 1926-1928 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Members and Officers of the New York State Legislature, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Members and Officers of the New York State Legislature, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - N, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - N, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - National Get Out the Vote Club Pamphlet on Voting, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - New York State Anti-Vivisection Society: "The Dog's Fourteen Points", Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - New York League of Women Voters Pamphlets, 1929; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - O, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - O, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ogdensburg, 1925-1929; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - P, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - P, 1926; 1928-1930; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - P, 1926; 1928-1930; Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Pamphlet: "The Case Against Capital Punishment in California", 1929 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pamphlet on the Farmers Tax Burden, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Paul, 1924-1929; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Prohibition (1 of 2), 1932; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Prohibition (2 of 2), 1932; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Q, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - R, 1922; 1924-1927; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - R, 1927-1930; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Regional Market Needs in New York State Pamphlet, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Release and Speeches, 1927-1928; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Relief Corps, 1929; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Republican Campaign Songs and Propaganda, 1928; 1930; 1936; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Republican National Committee Pamphlets, 1920; Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Republican Pamphlets on Tariffs, 1927-1928; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Republican State Bulletins, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Republican State Convention Program, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Republican Party Correspondence and Programs, 1920; 1922; 1924; 1928; Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Republican Party Membership and Delegates, 1921-1924; 1928; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Republican Party Membership and Delegates, 1921-1924; 1928; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Republican Party Pamphlets, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Republican Women's National Executive Committee Pamphlets, 1920; Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - S, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - S, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Seed Bill, 1925-1926; Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - State Aid for Education, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - State Service Magazine, 1924-1925 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - State Service Magazine, 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - State Publicity, 1927; 1929-1931; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - State Publicity Bill, 1927-1929 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - St. Lawrence County Republican Organization Pamphlets, 1917; 1928 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - T, 1922; 1924-1927; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Taxation, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - U, 1926-1927 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - V, 1922; 1924-1927; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vetoed Senate Bills--Thayer, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - W, 1924-1927; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - W, 1928-1930; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Bills, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Women's National Republican Club Pamphlets, 1924; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Women's National Republican Club Pamphlets on Alf Landon Campaign, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Senate Files, 1914-1948; 2; 7.2 cubic ft.
  Graves spent 14 years in the New York State Senate. This series contains political, legislative and personal correspondence sometimes separated by subject, author or location and sometimes filed together in less defined groupings. Also included in this series are Senate bills, campaign materials, reference materials, and political and civic organization materials. As she was no longer in the Assembly and campaigning for a seat in the Senate, Graves' unsuccessful 1932 Senate campaign materials are part of this collection.
  The series is arranged chronologically.
  - Political Correspondence and Publications, 1914; 1924; 1927-1928; 1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Political Correspondence and Publications, 1914; 1924; 1927-1928; 1934; Undated (Flat-file 3)
  - H. W. Livermore, 1919-1922; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1932 Senate Campaign (1 of 3), 1922; 1925; 1931-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1932 Senate Campaign (2 of 3), 1922; 1925; 1931-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1932 Senate Campaign (3 of 3), 1922; 1925; 1931-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1932 Senate Campaign, 1922; 1925; 1931-1932; Undated (Flat-file 4)
  - Pure Paint Bill, 1923; 1930-1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gouverneur, 1926-1928; 1935; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Franklin & St. Lawrence County, 1926; 1928; 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Literature Including Rhoda Fox Graves, 1926; 1933-1934; 1938; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Papers, 1926; 1936-1937; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - K-L Correspondence, 1926; 1937-1938; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - State Publicity--Boland, etc., 1927; 1929-1931; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Christian Science, 1927; 1929; 1932-1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - DeKalb, 1928; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - International Bridge Bill, 1928-1931; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Invitations to Speak, 1928-1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Potsdam, 1929; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Education League, 1929-1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Grange, 1929; 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1930-1931; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Speeches and Statements, 1930-1931; 1933-1935; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Jones, Annette C., 1930-1932; 1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Clark, Anne Birrell, 1930; 1932-1933; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Speeches and Correspondence, 1930; 1932; 1937; 1939; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gouverneur, 1930; 1940-1942; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - McCann, Anable Parker, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - State Employees Retirement Fund, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Barney, Bradley L., 1931-1933; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Little Red School House, 1931; 1935-1936; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Agricultural Poison, 1931; 1939 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - The Jeffersonian, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Appel, Lynn, 1932-1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Milk Classification [Marketing and Resale], 1932-1934; 1940-1941; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Help From RFG, 1932; 1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Undulant Fever: Dairy, 1932; 1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Welch, Billy, 1932; 1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Jones, Fred, 1932; 1935-1937; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Republican Campaign Material [Not RFG], 1932; 1936-1938; 1941; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Shakespeare Club, 1932-1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Martha Washington Republican Club, 1933; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ernest Botting Case, 1933; 1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Canton-- Clare-- Clifton-- Colton, 1933; 1937; 1939-1943; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Child Labor Booklets, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Senatorial Campaign, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Senatorial Campaign, 1934; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Congratulatory Letters and Other Correspondence (1 of 2), 1934; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Congratulatory Letters and Other Correspondence (2 of 2), 1934; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Political, Legislative and Personal Correspondence, 1934; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Telegrams, Letters Read After 1934 Election and Answers, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - G.O.P. Albany Weekly Newsletters and Economic Council Letters, 1934-1935; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Legislation and Calendar of Bills, 1934-1934; 1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Bills and Correspondence, 1934-1937; Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Invitations, 1934; 1937 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Canton--Van Whittemore, 1934; 1941-1943; Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Expense Accounts and Receipts, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - International Reform Federation Pamphlets on Gambling, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Senate Bills, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Women Republican, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Transcript of Hearing On Mineral Springs, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Members, Officers and Standing Committees, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Milk Control, 1935-1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mineral Springs Commission (1 of 2), 1935-1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mineral Springs Commission (2 of 2), 1935-1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Johnson, Harold, 1935-1938; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Labor, 1935; 1938; 1940-1942; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Joint Legislative Committee to Investigate Mineral Water of the State, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - G.O.P. Speeches--R.F. Graves, 1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence, 1936; Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Red School House, 1936; Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Seeds, 1936; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Child Labor Amendment, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Pamphlets and Printouts, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - State, City and County Republican Committees, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - D- Correspondence, 1936-1938 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Political and Legislative Correspondence and Bills, 1936-1938 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Christian Science Worlds Fair Activities, 1936-1939 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Mineral Springs Commission, 1936-1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Social Security, 1936-1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Political, Legislative and Personal Correspondence, 1936-1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Congratulations and Other Correspondence (1 of 2), 1936-1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Congratulations and Other Correspondence (2 of 2), 1936-1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dillon, John J., 1936-1937; 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Conservation, 1936; 1939; 1940-1943; 1948; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Legislation Introduced by Senator Graves, 1936; 1940; 1942-1943; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Assorted Correspondence and Christian Science Material, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Milk, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Agriculture, 1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dillon--McElroy--Young Bill, 1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dillon--McElroy--Young Bill, 1937; Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Milk Correspondence (1 of 2), 1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Milk Correspondence (2 of 2), 1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Milk--Letters and Papers, 1937; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - E--Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - M--Miscellaneous [Legislative Correspondence], 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - St. Lawrence, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Berghold, 1937-1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Malone, 1937-1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Messena Letters, 1937-1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Optometry, 1937-1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Parker, Frank A., 1937-1938; 1940; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Agriculture, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Elrich, Harold (Including Petroleum Industry Investigation), 1937-1939; Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Labor, 1937-1939; Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Black Lake Camp--A.M. Wade, 1937-1943; Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - DePeyster--DeKalb, 1937; 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Cooperative Corporations Law, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - G--Correspondence, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Legislative Manual [Red Book] Requests, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Public Hearing Before the Senate Committee on Public Education, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Wage & Hour Bill, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - B--Correspondence, 1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Joint Legislative Committee on Interstate Cooperation, 1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Legislature, 1938; Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Conservation, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Farmer's File, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Fellows, A., 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - J. Dillon, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Jobs Wanted & Help, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Saranac Lake, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Cheese, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Crime, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Dairymen's League, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Dewey, 1939-1939; Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Education, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Franklin County, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Insurance, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Legislation, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Massena, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Milk Letters and Speeches, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Police, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Roger-Allen Law Letters, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - State Officials, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Taxes, 1938-1939; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1938-1939; 1942; 1946; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dr. Reynolds--W.K. Maffatt: Milk, 1938-1941; Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture, 1938-1943; Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Harold, 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - G.O.P. County Committee Members, 1938; 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Franklin County and St. Lawrence County Library Bills, 1938; 1940; 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Franklin County, 1938; 1942-1946; Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ogdensburg, 1938; 1944-1945; Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Republican Primary Ballot and Written List of Bills, 1938; 1947 (Flat-file 5)
  - Alcoholic Beverages Control Board, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Adie, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Against the Nunan--Allen Bill, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - American Defense Society Incorporated, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Billboards, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Brief by Dairymen's League: Legislative Hearing on the Nunan--Allen Bill, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Centralization of Schools Bill, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Christian Science, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Citizens Union, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Clubs, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Coudert Bill: NYC Resident's Opposition, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Deaf--Wastchel Bill, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Dog License, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Economic Council, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Ehrlick, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Food Law, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Forum, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - H--Correspondence, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Health, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Help From RFG, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Hyde, Gertrude, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - International News, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Jaeckle, E., 1939 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Loomis, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - M--Correspondence, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Maple Syrup Law, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Morissette, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Mortgage, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Motor Vehicle Bureau, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Musician, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - National League of Teachers & Mothers, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Ogdensburg, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - P--Correspondence, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pension, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Press Letters, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Railroads, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Requests For Bills, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Robert I. Millozi c/o Coatsworth & Diebold, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Roger- Allen Milk Bill: Telegrams and Postcard, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Rose, L.A. (Milk), 1939 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Science Bill, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - St. Joseph Lead, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Weights and Measures, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Wicks [Bill], 1939 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - W--Correspondence, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Agriculture Bill [Nunan-Allen Bill], 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bang's Disease, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Civil Service, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fuel, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Funeral Letters, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Graves, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hospital, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hotel, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Housing, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Harold B., 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Legislation For Women, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)